## Ryan O'Regan

## PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am currently studying software engineering at Ara Institute of Canterbury. I am highly proficient with navigating and teaching complex computer systems, am very self-motivated and am willing to learn. My career goals are to get experience in the industry and progress into the software development space.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Craigmore Sustainables Christchurch, New Zealand May 2023 – February 2024 IST Support Analyst Working full-time hand tickets from clients, many

## Kathmandu – Head Office Christchurch, New Zealand July 2021 – May 2023

## Kathmandu – Riccarton Outlet Christchurch, New Zealand Nov 2018 – July 2021

Working full-time handling BAU incidents and problem tickets from clients, managing all software and hardware across the company while continuously exploring and implementing enhancements to our systems.

## Customer Service Officer/Senior CSO

Communication Technology

I worked full-time initially as a CSO handling tickets, phone calls and live chats from customers before being promoted to Senior in April 2022. My workload consisted of managing a team of 15 in BAU, handling customer escalations and collaborating with the wider business on system projects.

## Sales advisor

I worked part-time in a team environment communicating to customers in store and over the phone, make sales using EFTPOS and retail software, understand and explain product knowledge, manage deliveries, count, move stock on the shop floor, and uphold store values and competencies.

#### **EDUCATION**

2023

University of Canterbury	Bachelor of Science
Christchurch, New Zealand	Papers studied included Biology,
2017 - 2019	Psychology, Chemistry and Statistics. Graduated with a 7.54 GPA endorsed in Ecology.
Ara Institute of Canterbury	Diploma in Information &

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Experience with full Office Suite
- Microsoft D365, Jira, DevOps, Magento, Azure AD (Entra ID), Defender/Exchange/365 Admin
- AWS, Django, Apache, React, Vite
- Experience imaging and setting up companywide laptops, via Intune and NinjaOne remote management solutions
- Proficient in Python, JS, TypeScript, HTML, CSS and Powershell
- Experience deploying PWA and front-end websites with database connections

#### PERSONAL SKILLS

## Communication skills

I have been responsible for providing customers from all walks of life with answers to their queries, as well as friendly meaningful communication that leaves them with a positive impression of the company I represent.

## Self-Management

My work experience and academic background, including my undergraduate degree, have instilled a strong sense of self-management. I consistently meet deadlines and maintain high standards in my work, ensuring tasks are completed on time and with precision.

## **Problem-Solving**

Working in customer-centric and fast-paced environments has developed my problem-solving abilities. I've learned to think on my feet to make sales and keep customers satisfied. Additionally, I've gained expertise in handling escalations with a firm but fair approach.

## Reliable and Willingness

I take my work seriously and exhibit unwavering reliability and enthusiasm. My dedication is evident through my punctuality and strong work ethic. I'm always eager to learn and embrace the challenge of acquiring new skills.

#### **Teamwork**

With extensive experience working in team settings, I foster a positive team environment that is both focused and supportive. I encourage collaboration and contribute to a cohesive and productive team dynamic.

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

#### Kathmandu MVP Award

2022

In recognition of outstanding commitment to supporting the launch of Microsoft D365 across the company.

## NZIML Leadership courses

2022

I have successfully undertaken Leadership courses in Managing Others and Effective Communication. Nationally recognized standards.

## University of Canterbury Summer Research Scholarship

2020

I completed a Summer Scholarship with the Freshwater Ecology Research Group (FERG) in 2020, performing original research and experiments with invasive tadpoles in the Cass region.

#### **INTERESTS**

Board/computer games; gardening; weightlifting/bouldering; reading; current events.

**REFEREES:** References available upon request.